I just want to hurry up and get going.
It's delicious.
I'm off!
When I realized...
Love Hughie
Cute!
Bombinos
Pombinos
This would be a bonbinos.
Wow.
I hope it opens.
Is it hot?
Are you okay?
Oh.
Oh, I got it.
Mmm-hmm.
You're all here.
I can see it now.
It says "good moe" on it.
I like it.
It's in Japanese.
It says "moe-te-giru".
It's interesting.
Interesting.
Interesting
interesting
Interesting.
Can I open it for a second?
It's so big. It's so big.
I'm so hungry.
I don't think I'll be eating today.
I'll put on my hotel coat.
Can I take this with me?You want to take the whole thing?
I don't want it.
I'll keep it.
I'm Ukrainian, you know. I'm not popular or anything.
Let me see some of that salami.
Okay, okay, okay.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, my God!
Looks delicious.
Yeah, it's really good.
Oh, man.
We can't just go like that.
Oh, no.
Where are you going? Out of the way?
Ya-ya?
Looks so good!
Oh, man!
Oh, my God!
I can't cut this!
Help!
Oh, man!
Oh, my God, that sounds great!
This is bad!
Oh!
It's stuck!
This is bad!
Oh, no!
It's stuck!
Oh, it's stuck to that!
See you soon.
What language?
Nyoo.
Nyos.
Nyos.urinary fluid
Don't you want to glove up?
Here.
Wrong hand.
Right hand.
Checque.
Okay, okay.
Let's lose the chopsticks, too.
And...
This one, too.
One more time.
Wow.
The shellfish.
It's okay. It's okay.
Did it go in your eye?
Yeah, I got it.
That's nice.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
You're getting better.
Smells good.
Seino.
I got this.
Can you see it?
It's delicious.
We can't burn the bombinos.
I think I'll eat the bombinos first.
Bombinos. But they look delicious.
We've already had bonbinos.
Bon-binos until now.
I guess that means it's good, right?
Bon appétit!
Oh my God!
It's so good!It's so good!
Can I touch it?
Hot, hot, hot!
Can you get it?
I can get it.
It's so clean.
I'll just get the shells.
Thank you. Thank you.
You got it?
I got it!
Bon appétit!
Yeah!
Is it good?
It's good, right?
Oh, my God! It's so good!
It's just soy sauce.
It's much better.
Delicious.
Delicious!
Ah!
Oh!
Ta-da!
Flowers are red too!
It's so good!
Delicious?
So juicy!
Delicious!
I'm so glad I bought this!
They're so good!
I can have one more each!
Wait a minute!
Where did you touch?
I'm getting all hot and bothered.
I'm getting a little firmer.Whatcha-o
What-tea-tea.
Okay, it's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
That's good.
Is it hot in here?
Not at all.
How do I make it easier to fall?
One time.
Open one.
Oh, that's good.
Is it good?
She's crying so hard.
It's so good.
Tears of joy.
I haven't had good food for a long time.
It took a lot of effort to eat it.
That's right.
Oh, it's delicious.
Delicious.
It's hot and delicious.
It's good.
Oh, it's great!
Kanamin taking a selfie
Everyone take selfie time!
Delicious!
It's a little hot.
Let's eat!
Thank you for the food!
All done!
What did you eat?
I ate it all!
You did your best!
Spiced it up!
It was so good!
Well, let's work on cleaning up now!Then let's do our best to clean up now!
I'll do my best!
Yay-o!
Then... it's too shabby, isn't it?
It's not good.
I'm just clearing out this tree to burn it, but it's not gonna burn anymore, so...
Calamine and Pioninmadoc.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Whew!
Hey!
Here you go.
Got it?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Maybe it's...
It's raining.
Tee.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, bye.
You can go ahead and zap in there now.
Keep your clothes on.
All of them, really?
How do you like it?
Here we go.
I don't know if it'll hold.
Wait a minute.
I only use machines in my life.
Oh! Here it comes, here it comes!
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God! Isn't it great?
It's so cool!
It looks like a pineapple!
Wow!Amazing!
Go, go, go, go!
Go over there, where it's not blacked out, and you'll see lots of fish!
Wow! Wanna go check it out?
Wanna go check it out?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, near that boat.
It's on fire.
They went to see the fish.
The pine cones are making it look like it's on fire.
All right. - All right.
That's good.
There it is?
Kaname?
Are you there?
You don't have to go that far!
I'm here!
There they are!
You don't have to go that far.
Do you know where they are? Calamintopio.
I don't know. The camera doesn't do it justice.
Um, if I walk, they'll run away.
Yeah, I know.
Look, there they are.
He's wiggling around... over here.
More on our side.
There it is.
You don't see it?
Yay.
I'm done cleaning up!
The day is coming to an end.
Thank you. You two washed up.
It's a lot of work, isn't it?
It's a mess.
Cleaning up is the hardest part.
You know, getting ready...I'm getting ready. I'm just getting ready.
I don't care. We're going to eat good food.
Cleanup is the hard part.
And, you know, I learned a lot at camp.
I learned a lot.
Let's come back when it's warmer.
It's so nice.
It was cold today.
I'll come back again.
Please take me with you.
Let's go.
I love the outdoors.
Invite the other members.
It was fun.
Bye bye.
Hey guys, subscribe to our channel.
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!
Thank you very much.
Bye, bye, bye.
Yay! Finish the bonfire and come back to the hotel.
I know, it's beautiful. It's so beautiful.
Did you see the wilderness? You didn't see it?
No, just a little bit. Nature was so beautiful.
I'm going to take a bath now.
I'm so tired. I'm so glad. I can smell the fire.
I'm already washed from the bonfire.
I'm off.
Bye bye!
Let's eat.
Bye bye.
Good morning, Pio.
What's up?
Good morning, Pio. Good morning.
I don't see anyone.
I don't know.
She's not here.She's not here.
She's missing.
Good morning.
You're a little late this morning, aren't you?
You're late this morning.
Oh, by the way...
I see.
Get up early.
Kanami has some work.
Kanami's running late, so...
Just the two of us today.
We're going to sleep well.
I'm going back to Yamanashi for sightseeing.
Here we go.
It's sunny today.
So far.
This afternoon, it's a little bit old-fashioned.
I'll enjoy it.
Hey, guys!
Here we are!
We've arrived!
Here we are at the food station!
You know, you can go around Kawaguchi Lake
Around and around the lake
We're at the food station!
Let's go.
I'm so hungry.
I said, "Aren't you hungry? I said.
I'm starving.
Is Yamanashi famous for wine?
Famous, famous.
I'm starving.
I've got my eye on something.I've got my eye on it.
Oh, man.
So you're just gonna go right now?
I haven't done it yet.
I mean, it's not even...
It's not even 10:00 yet.
Oh, shit.
Muscat, star employee.
Muscat, the star employee.
Do you have any background on this?
I haven't seen it.
I'm not waiting.
Look at this.
Looks delicious.
It looks so good.
I have strawberries.
Hey.
Wow!
Wow, it looks so good.
I love it.
Looks delicious.
Have you ever had it?
No, I haven't.
It's so good.
I'll eat it later... in the car.
It's some kind of ancient mine.
It's so cute.
It's amazing.
The smoked cheese is so good.
You grill it in a pan or something.
It's so good.
What is that?
Ikasuni garlic.
Oh, wow.
This?
There's a lobby downstairs.There's a lobby downstairs.
Oh, yeah.
Looks delicious.
Amazing.
Plums and...
What's that? Bamboo?
Bamboo pasta.
Pasta
What's Yamanashi?
I don't get it.
You're right.
That's what we got.
That's something!
It has nothing to do with that.
That's it.
But strawberries...
HITO-chan is all about strawberries.
Delicious!
I've never had this before.
White strawberries.
What?
They're not coated?
No, it's not.
Bon appétit!
Sounds good.
Yeah, it's good.
Yeah. Yum. Yum.
Yum.
Yummy.
Yum. Yum.
I didn't even look at him.
But they looked at me like I was crazy.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's so good!
Miyu bought it for me.
Sour.Sour.
Let's go.
Let's go to the launch of Guess
Let's go
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
It's gonna be okay.
Oh, you're okay.
Nice.
The guy next to me is a good driver.
Let's go! Let's go!
How long do you think it'll take?
I have to know.
Twenty minutes.
Not long.
You've never been.
You can walk around and eat, but if you do it, you'll be in trouble.
I'm serious.
Like big rice crackers.
Or dumplings.
But if you want to eat, we can eat.
Let's eat a lot.
It's the least we can do.
We're going to destroy the turret for the turret, and then we're going to push it down.
I like the rules, don't you?
The acquisition card has been inserted. It's been inserted.
It's a little full. I wonder which way out.
This way.
This way. - This is the way out.
Which way do we go?
I don't know at first.
We're only allowed to go this way.
Then go in the direction of Kofu.
We're not going to Kofu, we're going to Kawaguchi Ward.
What's the background music?Well, what about some background music?
Background music?
Sing for us?
No Japanese music.
What would you like for background music?
Straight line song?
Anything that plays.
Anything.
What do you like?
I'll be standing up in a minute.
Today, when I woke up this morning, I couldn't open my throat.
I gargled a lot.
The first thing I did when I woke up was gargle.
My mouth is so thin.
But we sing a lot in the car.
We've been singing since a while ago.
We sing in the room too.
We put on music anyway.
I'd like to do that.
Okay, then.
Until the rum.
And then?
Thank you all for coming today. Let's have some fun in the tunnel.
Where the hell have you been?
We're gonna have to move to the back.
Where are you?
Are we there yet? In the city.
Not yet?
Not yet.
I hope he's arrived safely.
It's hot out.
It's hot.
Out?
What's that?Huh?
Huh?
What's up?
Oh, my God.
It's the multitude of refugees.
I'm here!
I thought I'd leave you something.
To the notes of the sun...
Fireworks... that's what they want to sing about.
Oh, it's so bright.
Love doesn't mean compensation
How big will it get?
What should I do with this feeling
I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop
I'm aware of Love
It's a day for love
Taste it without leaving a drop
Ohtenagaa dark, dark, dark night, gazing at the stars all the time
HITO-CHAN
Yosamashii yosamashii yosamashii yosamashii
Chacha Chacha, a spell
You love, don't you?
Kanamin!
I don't like to show the back of my head, but here it is.
You know?
And where Kanamin was sitting.
Our bags are all over the place.
Put Mazyck on.
I can't do it yet.
I don't have mosaic skills.
Okay, then.
Let's see it now.
Let me see.
Show me everything, show me everything.
All of it.All of it.
Nothing to hide.
That's right.
YouTuber.
Let me show you.
Oh, you can see a little bit of heaven on Mt.
Look, it's too dirty already.
Fuji.
It's Mt.
See you later.
I'll do the eyeballs later.
Bye bye.
Up?
Oh, there it is.
One channel.
Yay!
We're here.
Where was it again?
Oshino-Hachikai
I got it.
Oshino Yakkai.
I remembered.
Oshihaha... Oshihaha border.
Hmm?
Oshi-no-Hachikai
Oshi-no-boundary
Oshi-no-Yoshikawa
I've been expecting it.
I've never had that idea before.
Oshi-no-Hachikai
Wow, beautiful.
Come with me.
Come with me.You wanna come with me?
Oh!
Wow, that looks cool.
Looks cool.
Cool.
It's gonna be cold in there.
Where are we fishing?
I don't know. But you said this way, right?
Isn't that it? In the parking lot.
But you said this way, right?
Do you want to look at a map?
I don't know if you can look at a map.
What's your guess?
What's...
What? What did we get caught up in?
I'll clear it up right here, right now.
What is it? What's that...
This is it. Where?
But, you know, there's no one over here.
That's not the Hakkai I know.
Doesn't that one look like the Hakkai I know? It's more like...
Where is it? No, in this case...
It's a map. It's a cell phone.
Oh, my God.
Do you recognize it?
Opposite of the stars.
Oh, it's this way!
I knew it!
Of course it is. How could I lie?
But don't you want to go to Hakkouzan, the castle that you know?
That's it. That's it. That's it.
You mean that's where we're going?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, so that's it.
It's a nice walking area until then.
Yeah, like that.Yeah, like.
Instead of going directly like that.
I wonder.
Can't we just go from there?
That's what I mean.
Wow, the cherry blossoms are still blooming.
And they're beautiful.
There's a little bit of green mixed in.
It's nice.
This way.
It's so cold!
My jacket, from yesterday.
It stinks.
I'm sorry.
I've got a HEATTECH, too.
Today and, uh, today and...
I only brought one.
It stinks.
I thought it's not normal to wear that.
You're right.
It's a cat.
Meow.
Cute!
There's a lot going on here.
The pond there is famous
Pond
Strawberry pond
There are a lot of strawberries.
I wonder...
Can we get some?
This place is famous.
I've never been from this side before.I've never been here before from this side.
Love.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right in the middle there.
Spring water.
Oh, that's Stetz.
That's it.
That's great.
Stets.
I'm TOKUSAN
TOKUSAN Members
I'm HITOCHAN
That's great.
Amazing, isn't it?
Beautiful.
It's so beautiful!
Yes, it is.
Wow, it's deep.
If you drop it, it's over.
Right?
Otan is a pushy little guy.
Oh, he's a mess.
Oh, he's so squashy.
Happy.
Wealthy.
Where do you eat? Where do you want to eat?
Where would you like to eat? ★Where would you like to eat?
Wealthy is good.
I was told it's easy to be rich.
I bought dumplings.
The soy sauce dumplings look delicious.
Want some? Want to take a picture? I'm fine.
It's okay.
They won't take a picture of me. I'm such a mess.
I'm running out of juice.
Bon appétit!Thank you for the food.
Here you go, boy.
Delicious?
Looks delicious.
Daifuku.
That's right.
First, Daifuku.
Big ones.
Here it comes.
Wow, wow, wow!
It's so stretchy.
Soft?
Yes, it is.
I'll take my piece of happiness.
It's so cute.
Yeah. Is it good?
Yeah, it's good!
Hey, it's warm, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is it gonna be warm?
It's coming down!
It's coming down?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm so happy.
Bye-bye.
Ta-da! Here comes the coat.
Yummy, yummy, yummy.
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy.
We both got the same one.
Ta-da!
Bon appétit.
Looks delicious!
Yes, that's why we ate it!
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious. It was so delicious.
It was so delicious! It was so filling and delicious!It was amazing, filling, and delicious.
The best.
Yes, that's it.
Our one and only trip to Yamanashi
Yes, it's a relationship
Yes, it's a relationship.
Thanks for watching.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
See you soon.